{
  "title": "Amharic Course Quizzes",
  "quizzes": [
    {
      "id": "symbol_to_name",
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "prompt": "Identify ሀ",
          "options": [
            "Ha",
            "Ye"
          ],
          "answer": "Ha"
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "prompt": "Identify ለ",
          "options": [
            "Le",
            "Ha"
          ],
          "answer": "Le"
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "prompt": "Identify መ",
          "options": [
            "Me",
            "Se"
          ],
          "answer": "Me"
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "prompt": "Identify ሰ",
          "options": [
            "Se",
            "Te"
          ],
          "answer": "Se"
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "prompt": "Identify ሸ",
          "options": [
            "She",
            "Le"
          ],
          "answer": "She"
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "prompt": "Identify ቀ",
          "options": [
            "Qe",
            "Be"
          ],
          "answer": "Qe"
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "prompt": "Identify ተ",
          "options": [
            "Te",
            "Se"
          ],
          "answer": "Te"
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "prompt": "Identify በ",
          "options": [
            "Be",
            "Te"
          ],
          "answer": "Be"
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "prompt": "Identify ነ",
          "options": [
            "Ne",
            "Ha"
          ],
          "answer": "Ne"
        },
        {
          "type": "multiple_choice",
          "prompt": "Identify የ",
          "options": [
            "Ye",
            "Ha"
          ],
          "answer": "Ye"
        }
      ]
    },
    {
      "id": "syllables",
      "questions": [
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ሀ order 1",
          "answer": "hä"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ሀ order 2",
          "answer": "hu"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ሀ order 3",
          "answer": "hi"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ሀ order 4",
          "answer": "ha"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ሀ order 5",
          "answer": "he"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ሀ order 6",
          "answer": "hə"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ሀ order 7",
          "answer": "ho"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ለ order 1",
          "answer": "lä"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ለ order 2",
          "answer": "lu"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ለ order 3",
          "answer": "li"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ለ order 4",
          "answer": "la"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ለ order 5",
          "answer": "le"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ለ order 6",
          "answer": "lə"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ለ order 7",
          "answer": "lo"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for መ order 1",
          "answer": "mä"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for መ order 2",
          "answer": "mu"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for መ order 3",
          "answer": "mi"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for መ order 4",
          "answer": "ma"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for መ order 5",
          "answer": "me"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for መ order 6",
          "answer": "mə"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for መ order 7",
          "answer": "mo"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ሰ order 1",
          "answer": "sä"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ሰ order 2",
          "answer": "su"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ሰ order 3",
          "answer": "si"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ሰ order 4",
          "answer": "sa"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ሰ order 5",
          "answer": "se"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ሰ order 6",
          "answer": "sə"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ሰ order 7",
          "answer": "so"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ሸ order 1",
          "answer": "šä"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ሸ order 2",
          "answer": "šu"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ሸ order 3",
          "answer": "ši"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ሸ order 4",
          "answer": "ša"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ሸ order 5",
          "answer": "še"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ሸ order 6",
          "answer": "šə"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ሸ order 7",
          "answer": "šo"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ቀ order 1",
          "answer": "qä"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ቀ order 2",
          "answer": "qu"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ቀ order 3",
          "answer": "qi"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ቀ order 4",
          "answer": "qa"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ቀ order 5",
          "answer": "qe"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ቀ order 6",
          "answer": "qə"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ቀ order 7",
          "answer": "qo"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ተ order 1",
          "answer": "tä"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ተ order 2",
          "answer": "tu"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ተ order 3",
          "answer": "ti"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ተ order 4",
          "answer": "ta"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ተ order 5",
          "answer": "te"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ተ order 6",
          "answer": "tə"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ተ order 7",
          "answer": "to"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for በ order 1",
          "answer": "bä"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for በ order 2",
          "answer": "bu"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for በ order 3",
          "answer": "bi"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for በ order 4",
          "answer": "ba"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for በ order 5",
          "answer": "be"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for በ order 6",
          "answer": "bə"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for በ order 7",
          "answer": "bo"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ነ order 1",
          "answer": "nä"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ነ order 2",
          "answer": "nu"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ነ order 3",
          "answer": "ni"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ነ order 4",
          "answer": "na"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ነ order 5",
          "answer": "ne"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ነ order 6",
          "answer": "nə"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for ነ order 7",
          "answer": "no"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for የ order 1",
          "answer": "yä"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for የ order 2",
          "answer": "yu"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for የ order 3",
          "answer": "yi"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for የ order 4",
          "answer": "ya"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for የ order 5",
          "answer": "ye"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for የ order 6",
          "answer": "yə"
        },
        {
          "type": "matching",
          "prompt": "Syllable for የ order 7",
          "answer": "yo"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}